http://dekalbtool.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeCompany ProfileExamples of Our WorkQuality AssuranceFacilitiesContact UsRequest for Quote
CAPABILITIES Metal Stamping Services Tool & Die Design & Manufacturing CNC Precision Milling 5 Axis Laser CuttingEquipment List EXAMPLES OF OUR WORKDeep Drawn Stamping of a Galvanized Steel Bus Roof Cap Design and Manufacturing of a Progressive Die for a Fluorescent Light Fixture Housing Design and Manufacturing of Transfer Tooling for the Automotive Industry CNC Machined Forged Billet 7050 Aluminum Aircraft Fittings for the Aerospace & Defense Industry Contract Metal Stamping for the Automotive Industry
Call:770.938.5605
Email:info@dekalbtool.com
Print This Page
Email This Page
Dekalb Tool & Die Privacy Policy
Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc. respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information CollectedIf you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via info@dekalbtool.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by OthersThis notice addresses only Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc.'s website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc. is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
CookiesDekalb Tool & Die, Inc.'s website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal InformationIf you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of InformationDekalb Tool & Die, Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy ChangesPlease note that Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc. and is effective as of December 19, 2011. This statement does not create an agreement between Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
Contact Us:Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc.2220 Stephens St.Tucker, GAPh: 770.938.5605Email: info@dekalbtool.comWebsite: www.dekalbtool.com
Dekalb Tool & Die, Inc.     2220 Stephens St., Tucker, GA     Ph: 770.938.5605     info@dekalbtool.com     Privacy     Site Map
Site Created by ThomasNet Web Solutions© 2011, dekalbtool.com
